techzil.com 2011-06-04

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy for www.techzil.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at sharat[@]techzil[.]com

TechZil respects your privacy and try not to misuse. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of TechZil.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates. TechZil will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you Do Not enter it on any of the forms on TechZil.

TechZil is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies** : A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows TechZil to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and TechZil does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds. Google and DoubleClick DART Cookies – Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site,  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet, Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Comments : **TechZil allows it’s visitors to comment on the site. We hold all rights to accept or reject any comments. While commenting on TechZil please refrain from using content that is not suitable. Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet .

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to TechZil and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.

In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through TechZil have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.  Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
